var questions = [
  {
    question: "Web pages are designed using?",
    option1: "HTML",
    option2: "JavaScript",
    option3: "CSS",
    option4: "JQuery",
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "____ makes websites dynamic.",
    option1: "HTML",
    option2: "JavaScript",
    option3: "CSS",
    option4: "Bootstrap",
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "What is HTML used for?",
    option1: "Skeleton of the website",
    option2: "Design",
    option3: "Make website dynamic",
    option4: "Database of website",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What is the HTML tag which defines a paragraph?",
    option1: "<script>",
    option2: "<p>",
    option3: "<hr>",
    option4: "<br>",
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "What does the <script> tag in HTML do?",
    option1: "Define the styling of the page",
    option2: "Includes images to the page",
    option3: "Includes JavaScript code in the page",
    option4: "Defines meta information",
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Bootstrap is a ______",
    option1: "JavaScript framework",
    option2: "HTML Library",
    option3: "Programming language",
    option4: "A CSS framework",
    answer: 4
  },
  {
    question: "What is the CSS property which helps to curve the border of and element?",
    option1: "border-radius",
    option2: "border-width",
    option3: "curve",
    option4: "curvature",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What does DOM imply?",
    option1: "Documentary object modelling",
    option2: "Data object manipulation",
    option3: "Data object model",
    option4: "Document Object Model",
    answer: 4
  },
  {
    question: "Which CSS property hides or shows an element?",
    option1: "hide",
    option2: "visual",
    option3: "display",
    option4: "flex",
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "What is the HTML tag which creates an image element?",
    option1: "<image>",
    option2: "<photo>",
    option3: "<img>",
    option4: "<pic>",
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "JavaScript statements should end with a ____",
    option1: "comma",
    option2: "exclamation",
    option3: "slash",
    option4: "semi colon",
    answer: 4
  }
]
